U.S. Wage, Hour and Public Contracts Division Records of Special Industry Committees for Puerto Rico 5444
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
U.S. Wage, Hour and Public Contracts Division Records of Special Industry Committees for Puerto Rico
1939-1965
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
U.S. Wage, Hour and Public Contracts Division
5444
9 cubic feet
9 linear ft.
Records (documents).
Records of Special Industry Committees on Puerto Rico.
5649169
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, May 07, 2013
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 13, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Wages -- Puerto Rico; Hours of labor -- Puerto Rico; Wages -- United States.; Hours of labor -- United States.; Wages -- Law and legislation -- Puerto Rico; Hours of labor -- Law and legislation -- Puerto Rico; Wages -- Law and legislation -- United States.; Hours of labor -- Law and legislation -- United States.; Puerto Rico.; United States. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Divisions.
5649169
- Special Industry Committee no.1 (1939). (Box 1)
  - Industry Committee No. 1 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Transcript of Hearings-Apparel Industry Committee No.2 - Book 1 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Industry Committee No. 2 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Transcript f Hearings - Apparel Industry No. 2 - Book 3(1) (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Transcript of Hearings - Apparel Industry No. 2 - Book 4 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Special Industry Committee no.2 (1939). (Box 2)
  - Transcript of Hearings-Apparel Industry Committee No.2 - Book 7(1) (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Transcript of Hearings-Apparel Industry Committee No.2 - Book 7(2) (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Transcript of Hearings-Apparel Industry Committee No.2 - Book 6(1) (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Transcript of Hearings-Apparel Industry Committee No.2 - Book 6(2) (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Transcript of Hearings-Apparel Industry Committee No.2 - Book 5 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Transcript of Hearings-Apparel Industry Committee No.2 - Book 8 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Special Industry Committee no.2 (1939). (Box 3)
  - Transcript of Hearings - Apparel Industry Comm. #2 - Book 9 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Transcript of Hearings - Apparel Ind. Comm. 2 - Book 10 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Digest of Textile Wage Record (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Transcript of Hearings - Apparel Industry Comm. 2 -Book 9 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Apparel Industry - Findings and Opinions of the Administrator (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Special Industry Committee no.2 (1939); no.3 (1944); no.4 (1955). (Box 4)
  - Industry Committee #2 Ctd. (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Special Industry Committee No. 3 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Industry Committee #4 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Economic Report - Part 1 - Hat Industry (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Economic Report - Part 2 - Hat Industry (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Special Industry Committee no.4 (1955); no.6 (1939); no.7 (1950); no.8 (1950); no.10 (1951); no.11 (1953); no.16 (1940); no.17 (1941); no.18 (1955); no.19 (1955); no.20 (1956). (Box 5)
  - Committee #4 Ctd. (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Industry Committee #6 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Industry Comm. #7 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Industry Comm. #8 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Industry Comm. #10 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Industry Comm. #11 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Industry Comm. #12 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Industry Comm. #13 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Industry Comm. #14 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Industry Comm. #15 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Industry Comm. #16 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Industry Comm. #17 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Industry Comm. #18 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Industry Comm. #19 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Industry Comm. #20 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Special Industry Committee no.21 (1941); no.23 (1941); no.27 (1942); no.29 (1957); no.32 (1957); no.34 (1941); no.35 (1957); no.36 (1957); no.37 (1941); no.38 (1958); no.39 (1958). (Box 6)
  - Industry Comm. #21 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Industry Comm. #23 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Economic Report - Gray Iron Jobbing Foundry Industry (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Industry Comm. #27 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Industry Comm. #29 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Industry Comm. #32 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Digest of Transcript - Hearing on Recommendation of Industry Committee No. 32 For the Knitted Outerwear Industry (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Industry Comm. #34 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Industry Comm. #35 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Industry Comm. #36 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Industry Comm. #37 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Industry Comm. #38 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Industry Comm. #39 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Special Industry Committee no.40 (1958); no.41 (1958); no.42 (1958); no.43 (1942); no.44 (1958); no.45 (1958); no.47 (1942); no.48 (1960); no.49 (1942); no.50 (1942). (Box 7)
  - Industry Committee No. 40 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Industry Committee No. 41 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Industry Committee No. 42 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Industry Committee No. 43 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Industry Committee No. 44 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Industry Committee No. 45 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Industry Committee No. 46 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Industry Committee No. 47 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Industry Committee No. 48 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Industry Committee No. 49 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Industry Committee No. 50 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Special Industry Committee no.51 (1961); no.52 (1942); no.53 (1962); no.54 (1962); no.55 (1962); no.56 (1962). (Box 8)
  - Industry Committee No. 51 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Industry Committee No. 52 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Industry Committee No. 53 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Industry Committee No. 54 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Industry Committee No. 55 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Industry Committee No. 56 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Special Industry Committee no.57 (1962); no.58 (1962); no.59 (1962); no.60 (1943); no.61 (1962); no.62 (1943); no.65 (1943); no.68 (1943); no.72 (1965). (Box 9)
  - Industry Committee No. 57 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Industry Committee No. 58 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Industry Committee No. 59 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Industry Committee No. 60 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Industry Committee No. 61 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Industry Committee No. 62 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Industry Comm. No. 65 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Industry Committee No. 68 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Industry Comm. No. 72 (Box 9, Folder 9)